<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mind Mingle</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="no_account">No account?</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="type_your_message">Type your message...</string>
    <string name="worry">Tell us what worries you today...</string>
    <string name="add_note">Add a note</string>
    <string name="search_here">Search here...</string>
    <string name="_1">1. Most people will respond with rudeness to rudeness.</string>
    <string name="answer1">almost always;</string>
    <string name="answer2">often;</string>
    <string name="answer3">sometimes;</string>
    <string name="answer4">accidentally;</string>
    <string name="answer5">very rarely.</string>
    <string name="nextq">Next question</string>
    <string name="_2">2. Most people don\'t believe in anything new until they experience it for themselves.</string>
    <string name="itog">Result</string>
    <string name="closetest">Complete the test</string>
    <string name="_3">3. Someone who completely trusts other people is often in a difficult position.</string>
    <string name="_4">4. Most people only work at full strength if they are forced to do so.</string>
    <string name="_5">5. Even the most heinous criminals have at least a modicum of decency.</string>
    <string name="q14">Do you often feel that injustice surrounds you?</string>
    <string name="ay">yes</string>
    <string name="an">no</string>
    <string name="q24">Do you often worry about the future?</string>
    <string name="q34">Do you have trouble falling asleep because of worries?</string>
    <string name="q44">Do you feel tired even after a night\'s sleep?</string>
    <string name="q54">Do you often feel irritated or stressed?</string>
    <string name="q21">You have unexpectedly achieved success with someone who you dislike. Will your opinion of this person change, will he become more pleasant to you?</string>
    <string name="q22">Will you be able to captivate a person with your idea by talking to them only on the phone?</string>
    <string name="q23">Do you listen to opinions in disputes that you disagree with?</string>
    <string name="q42">Were you a universal favorite in childhood – both children and adults?</string>
    <string name="q52">Do you like to look in the mirror?</string>
    <string name="q62">Do you often hear compliments addressed to you, and unselfish and sincere ones?</string>
    <string name="q72">Do you know how to avoid unpleasant questions without offending the other person?</string>
    <string name="q82">Do your lines "creep" up when writing?</string>
    <string name="q13">Do you think most people can be trusted or should you be careful when interacting with others?</string>
    <string name="a13">Most people can be trusted.</string>
    <string name="a23">You need to be careful when interacting with others.</string>
    <string name="q32">Could you say that people tend to be useful to others more often than not, or do they only think about themselves?</string>
    <string name="a33">They strive to be useful to others.</string>
    <string name="a43">They only think about themselves.</string>
    <string name="q33">Do you think most people would try to deceive you if they had the opportunity, or would they behave honestly?</string>
    <string name="a53">They would have behaved honestly.</string>
    <string name="a63">They would have tried to cheat if they had the opportunity.</string>
    <string name="this_is_message_text">This is message text</string>
    <string name="r1t4">High degree of stress: The results indicate a high level of stress. It is recommended to seek the help of a qualified professional, such as a psychologist or psychiatrist, to receive support and advice on stress management.</string>
    <string name="r2t4">Average stress level: Your answers indicate an average stress level. This may be a sign that your stress level is within the normal range, but it\'s still worth paying attention to your emotional states. Try to find ways to deal with stress, such as regular physical activity, meditation, deep breathing, or counseling with a psychologist.</string>
    <string name="r3t4">Low stress: Your responses indicate a low level of stress. This is good, but it must be remembered that stress can change over time, and it is important to continue to take care of your emotional and psychological well-being. Regular rest, healthy eating, maintaining social connections, and time management can help maintain your well-being.</string>
    <string name="r1t2">You are convinced that you have a personal charm. It seems that this is the case, but in some situations you should be more self-critical of yourself and pay more attention not to yourself, but to the people around you.</string>
    <string name="r2t2">There is no doubt that you can be called a charming person. You are pleasant in communication, you have a sense of self-worth. You will not change your beliefs and character just to make someone adore you.</string>
    <string name="r3t2">You are not everyone\'s favorite just because you keep the charm to yourself. This is probably because you are a very indecisive person, because of your lack of confidence in your own abilities, you are not able to convince others of your rightness, even if the truth is on your side.</string>
    <string name="r4t2">You lack charm primarily because you don\'t love yourself. Look in the mirror more often and learn to notice your advantages. The shortcomings that can be corrected, correct, and which cannot be changed, turn into advantages, into your "highlight". When communicating with others, try to keep a sense of self-worth</string>
    <string name="r1t3">You have a high confidence score</string>
    <string name="r2t3">You have an average confidence score</string>
    <string name="r3t3">You have a low confidence score</string>
    <string name="r1t1">a high indicator;</string>
    <string name="r2t1">the average indicator tends to be high;</string>
    <string name="r3t1">the average indicator tends to be low;</string>
    <string name="r4t1">the indicator is low.</string>
    <string name="t1tf">Test 1</string>
    <string name="t11tf">Diagnosis of a manipulative relationship</string>
    <string name="t2tf">Test 2</string>
    <string name="t22tf">Do you have charm?</string>
    <string name="t3tf">Test 3</string>
    <string name="t33tf">M. Rosenberg\'s scale of trust</string>
    <string name="t4tf">Test 4</string>
    <string name="t44tf">A psychological test to determine the level of stress</string>
</resources>